# Resume of Jayde Boardman

Email: jaydeboardman@outlook.com

Phone: 0422656062

GitHub Profile: <a href="https://github.com/J-boardman/">https://github.com/J-boardman/</a>

Personal Portfolio: https://i-boardman.github.io/portfolio/

## **Current Career Objectives**

Through my current studies in web development, I have found a lifelong passion in software development. I believe I have now reached a level of knowledge that would allow me to excel in a full time professional setting, where I can absorb and learn from industry leading best practices and intermediate / advanced development methods. I hope to find an employer that will allow me to experience continued growth and learning from being immersed in an enterprise level application / project, with a conductive team environment with other experienced and skillful developers.

### **Work Experience**

#### **Ecolife Solutions**

Jan 2022 - Oct 2022

Virtual Assistant / Data Entry

My current role at Ecolife Solutions has me handling the price listings and quotes, through both MYOB and Microsoft Excel. This requires a keen attention to detail, due to the strict requirement of data accuracy and consistency. Being a work from home role has also refined my own self-discipline and time management.

#### **Coles Supermarket**

Jan 2022 - Sep 2022

Nightfill Team Member

#### **Independent Contractor**

Sep 2017 - May 2021

#### Acoustic/Soundproofing Specialist

Responsible for the installation of Acoustic and Thermal insulation onto PVC Stormwater, PVC Condensate and Hot Water Copper pipe lines and stacks. Working in a construction environment refined my attention to detail and composure under pressure. Occasionally managed small teams of 2-5 people when the primary/lead worker on a building project. Notable projects as the primary worker include: The Johnson Apartments Spring Hill, Queensland State Velodrome and Queen Elizabeth II Jubilee Hospital Refurbishments.

Ecolife Solutions Jan 2014 – Dec 2017

Various roles: Acoustic/Soundproofing Specialist, Logistics, Factory Hand

Big W Jun 2011 – Jul 2014

Replenishment Associate

#### Education

TAFE QLD Graduating 2022

Diploma of Information Technology

Front End & Back End Web Development (ICT50220-FRTBCK)

Southbank, QLD

**Graduated 2013** 

#### **Bray Park State High School**

Queensland Certificate of Education (QCE) Certificate II in Information Technology (ICA20105) Certificate II in Business (BSB20107)

# References

Jasper Riedel Jasper.RiedelRutterford@tafeqld.edu.au

Teacher for technical subjects (HTML, CSS, JS, React, SQL, MongoDB)

TAFE Queensland

Kevin Bracken 0403 584 705

**General Manager of Ecolife Solutions** 

Geoff Coles 0402 087 349

Store Manager at Coles Strathpine